difrax.com 2018-08-21

# Privacy and Cookie Policy

This is the website of Difrax BV.  
Our company address is:

Rembrandtlaan 42  
3723 BK Bilthoven  
The Netherlands

Our mailing address is:  
Rembrandtlaan 42  
3723 BK Bilthoven  
The Netherlands

Our registration number with the Chamber of Commerce 300 700 52 Our B.T.W. number is 006 93 00 13 B01

* * *

This privacy policy sets out how this website (hereafter "Difrax") uses and protects any information that you give Difrax.com while using this website. Difrax is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Difrax.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

## What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * name
  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.

## What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by letting us know using our Contact Us information

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email us this request using our Contact Us information.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

## List of cookies we collect

The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.

Cookie Name| Cookie Description  
---|---  
FORM_KEY | Stores randomly generated key used to prevent forged requests.  
PHPSESSID | Your session ID on the server.  
GUEST-VIEW | Allows guests to view and edit their orders.  
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART | A link to information about your cart and viewing history, if you have asked for this.  
STF | Information on products you have emailed to friends.  
STORE | The store view or language you have selected.  
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE | Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.  
MAGE-CACHE-SESSID | Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.  
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE | Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.  
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE-SECTION-INVALIDATION | Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.  
MAGE-CACHE-TIMEOUT | Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.  
SECTION-DATA-IDS | Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.  
PRIVATE_CONTENT_VERSION | Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.  
X-MAGENTO-VARY | Facilitates caching of content on the server to make pages load faster.  
MAGE-TRANSLATION-FILE-VERSION | Facilitates translation of content to other languages.  
MAGE-TRANSLATION-STORAGE | Facilitates translation of content to other languages.  
_ga | Used to distinguish users.  
_gid | Used to distinguish users.  
_gat | Used to throttle request rate. If Google Analytics is deployed via Google Tag Manager, this cookie will be named _dc_gtm_.   
  
* * *

## How to contact us regarding our privacy policy?

If you wish to comment on our privacy policy, please contact us  
By email: [webshop@difrax.com](mailto:webshop@difrax.com) .

### Communication by e - mail

If you do not wish to receive e - mails from our company in the future, please contact us at the above address .

### About communication by letter

If your postal address via the web , you periodic mailings from usreceive with information about products and services . If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please contact us at the above address .

### Communication by telephone

If you give us your telephone number via the web, our company will only contact you if necessary to inform the orders you have placed online you.

If you wish to receive addressed advertising and / or commercial phone ( more ) please notify us via the website of the Foundation Infofilter : [www.infofilter.nl](http://www.infofilter.nl/) .

Our company may use consumer information for new purposes not yet included in our "privacy policy" . In that case , we will contact you before we use for these new purposes to notify you of changes to our regulations for the protection of personal data aware your data and give you the chance to refuse your participation .

Upon request we provide visitors to our site access to all information that we maintain about them . If you wish to access this information, please contact at the above address with us .

Upon request we offer visitors to our site the opportunity to correct information that we maintain about them , correct. If you wish to correct your personal information, please contact the above mentioned address.If you find that our site is not in accordance with our privacy policy , please contact us, please contact our company at the above address .
